entnet.org 2019-09-18

# Privacy Policy | American Academy of Otolaryngology-Head and Neck Surgery

The American Academy of Otolaryngology–Head and Neck Surgery (AAO-HNS) and American Academy of Otolaryngology–Head and Neck Surgery Foundation (AAO-HNSF) take the issue of privacy very seriously.

The AAO-HNS and AAO-HNSF do not sell, distribute, barter, or transfer personally identifiable information obtained from a user to a third party. Any information collected on any AAO-HNS/F website will only be used for the purpose stated. 

AAO-HNSF may provide mailing address information to third parties for single-use mailings for products and services that may be of interest to members. Email addresses, telephone numbers, or any other types of personally identifiable information are never provided to third party data processors.

AAO-HNS members who provide us with an email address may be added to the AAO-HNS email list or certain other private lists. The AAO-HNS email list is only for Academy/Foundation communications, such as  _OTO News  _or member communications. You will not receive third-party advertising or promotional material on this list.

The AAO-HNS and AAO-HNSF do not sell or distribute your email address to third parties, such as outside commercial, charitable, or professional organizations, under any circumstances. Unless you notify us otherwise, your email address may be available to other members through our online members-only directory.

The AAO-HNS may use "cookie" technology to aid in site navigation and registration and to obtain non-personal information from its online visitors. Such data may be collected and used in aggregate by the AAO-HNS/F to shape and direct the creation and maintenance of content and to determine the type of advertisement to be seen by site visitors. We do not extract personal information in this process nor do we provide this information to third parties. We also do not contact you based on information in your cookie file.

The AAO-HNS has taken steps to make all information received from our online visitors as secure as possible against unauthorized access and use. All information is protected by our security measures, which are reviewed periodically.

WARNING: This site contains links to other sites. The AAO-HNS/F assumes no responsibility for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
